[
	{
		"category": "mandarin",
		"answer": "Hello",
		"prompt": "Nǐhǎo (Nee how)"
	},

	{
		"category": "mandarin",
		"answer": "Thank you",
		"prompt": "Xièxiè (Shieh-shieh)"
	},

	{
		"category": "mandarin",
		"answer": "You’re welcome",
		"prompt": "Bù kèqì (Boo kuh-chi)"
	},

	{
		"category": "mandarin",
		"answer": "Good morning",
		"prompt": "Zǎo (Zhow)"
	},

	{
		"category": "mandarin",
		"answer": "Goodnight",
		"prompt": "Wǎn\"ān (One-un)"
	},

	{
		"category": "mandarin",
		"answer": "My name is…",
		"prompt": "Wǒ jiào... (Wuh jeow...)"
	},

	{
		"category": "mandarin",
		"answer": "I don\"t understand",
		"prompt": "Wǒ bù dǒng (Wuh boo dong)"
	},

	{
		"category": "mandarin",
		"answer": "Yes",
		"prompt": "Shì (Sheh)"
	},

	{
		"category": "mandarin",
		"answer": "No",
		"prompt": "Bù shì (Bu-sheh)"
	},

	{
		"category": "mandarin",
		"answer": "Bad",
		"prompt": "Bù hǎo (Boo-how)"
	}
];